50 years have passed.
But I do not age.
Time has lost its effect on me.
Yet the suffering continues.
Aku's grasp chokes the past,
present, and future.
Hope is lost.
Got to get back --
back to the past.
Samurai Jack.
Are you sure
she was the one?
Yes. I specifically saw her
asking about him.
Aku's bounty hunter?
I sense her evil.
Gotcha!
We will not let you
hurt the samurai.
Hurt?
No, I...
Look, I'm not
trying to hurt him.
I'm trying to find him.
He might be in trouble.
You are his friend?
I...don't know.
We are his friends.
It was long ago.
We were slaves.
Down, down,
you miserable beast!
Now go!
Come on! You're not
moving fast enough.
But then Jack came.
He risked his life
to save ours.
Miss, the bearded fella
you inquired about...
he got off here.
Thank you
for sharing your story.
You're supposed to get off
when you land!
I'm alive!
Doo do do do!
* I'm alive
Oh, right!
That samurai schmuck
broke my phone.
I got to tell Aku
that Jacky boy lost his sword.
Oh, well, I guess
I'm bunny hopping my way there.
Hippity hop, baby!
If you are one of Aku's
minions, we suggest you run.
If you are another,
then reveal yourself.
I seek the samurai.
No, I seek to help him.
He might be in danger.
A friend of Samurai Jack
is a friend of ours.
Come.
Welcome to our home.
None of this would exist
if it wasn't for him.
We were cursed...
bound to guard a magical portal.
The samurai was able
to defeat us,
but instead of using it
to fulfill his quest...
...he freed us.
An act of unmeasurable
sacrifice.
Later, we learned the curse
was of Aku's doing.
Have you seen him?
Has he
passed through here?
No. Since that day,
we have not seen him.
But we now stand
against Aku.
If he is ever in need,
we will be there.
Thank you.
I have to go.
Oh, man.
Oh. All this walking
is hard on my neck.
Hey, I made it!
I finally made it!
Aah!
What is the problemo, babe?
"No shirt, no shoes,
no body -- no entry!"?
Swing-a-ding-ding!
I am Aku's top bot,
the assassin with the sassin'.
"Aku's current top assassins --
one, Deathblow, two, Da-Bomb,
three, Scaramouche"?!
Oh, baby, I have
come down in the world.
How do you like that?
One day, you're
the star of the show,
the next, you're the third act
of a two-act play.
Well, this star
is a headliner, babe,
and once I tell Aku Jacky-o
lost his sword-o,
I'll be numero uno once more-o.
Hmm, now how am I gonna
get aboard the...
Oh, bing-o, baby!
Oh, drat!
Bow wow wow!
Bow wow wow, babe!
Bow wow heartbreaker.
Yeah, babe.
Dig this groovy cat.
Chow, chow, chowdity-chow chow,
baby cakes!
Whoo-hoo!
Numero uno, here I come!
That's 50 credits, bud.
Trust me, babe,
I'm good for it.
Yeah, well the last guy
I trusted did this to me!
Oh, it's all good, Babou.
Aku will give me anything
once he hears the news.
* Doo doo doo doo
Whoa, what a freak.
Looked like a talking penis.
Have you seen a samurai
come through here?
What do you want
with the samurai?
I think
he's in danger.
He needs my help.
Samurai drop!
* We will never forget you
till the day we die *
* Samurai
* Sa-sa-samurai
* Aku enslaved the children
* With his beats from hell
* But then he came and fought
the evil away *
* It was the samurai
* The samurai
* We will never forget you
till the day we die *
* Samurai
* Sa-sa-samurai
* Samurai-i-i-i-i-i-i-i-i
Thank you.
I will find him.
I must find him.
Aku, our lord and master,
is one with the darkness.
He was born from it.
It fills him
with infinite power.
We, too, must become
one with it.
We are forever grateful
and ever in your service.
Uh-oh.
Hey, babe, be a doll
and fetch us a drinky-poo.
Screw off, jerkhead!
I don't work here!
Oh, touchy.
A phone!
Scaramouche,
you are one lucky devil.
This is the operator.
Can I help you?
Yeah, emergency collect call
to Aku, babe.
Please say your name.
* Scaramouche
Please hold.
Hello?
Collect call from...
* Scaramouche
Will you accept
the charges?
Oh, uh...
Eh...
I guess.
Thank you.
Aku, my boss-man,
you will not believe
what I just went through, babe.
What?!
It's hard to hear you!
Eh, hold on a sec.
Hey, fellas, could you
keep it, like, down?
I'm trying to have
a conversation.
You talking to us?
Yeah, that's right, Rover.
I want you to keep
your barking to a minimum.
Rover?
Barking?
I think
he's calling us dogs.
Okay, little puppy,
you looked in a mirror lately?
Now, go get somebody
their slippers or something.
I'm on the line.
So I wanted to tell ya, Aku,
Jacko has lost --
Huh? What?
Forget it!
Usually me and the boys
would rip your head
from your body,
but looks like somebody
already did us the favor, eh?
So in lieu of that...
Dippity doo dang, babe.
Hey, man,
close the damn door!
You're letting
all the heat out!
What you want here,
Leaf Girl?
I'm looking
for Samurai Jack.
Huh, what'd you say?
I'm looking
for Samurai Jack.
Huh?
What's that?
Damn it, girl, speak up!
I'm looking
for Samurai Jack!
You're looking
for the samurai?!
Little girl, Samurai Jack is
the toughest S.O.B. out there.
Last time we fought,
he did...
this to me.
Ha! That's nothing!
Check me out!
These things are literally
holding me together!
Dude, really?
I used to go to the bathroom,
but now I go in a bag!
He busted me eye!
Man...those robotic cats
got nothin' on me!
'Cause back in the day,
I was a bad-ass sa-mu-rai!
I was da' samurai!
I was all about
the slicing and dicing!
Talkin' 'bout the...
Funk-a-chop!
The whack-a-hack!
And, of course,
the ever famous...
turkey carve!
But Samurai Jack enlightened me
to the true meaning
of being a samurai.
Shortly after,
I gave up my blade and top knot
and became the bartender here
at the place where we first met.
Uh...
That doesn't
sound bad at all.
That's because you ain't got
no soul, you robot fool!
I have returned!
I, Demongo,
have come to collect
the souls
of the greatest warriors.
But I see I have come
to the wrong place.
We got
some straight-up freaks
coming through
this place.
Are you the one
looking for the samurai?
Yes.
Are you his friend?
Follow the path north.
Who?
Samurai...
Jack?
You may witness, but you cannot
proceed any further.
Witness what?
The end.
Great warriors of past,
I welcome you.
This samurai has
failed his purpose
and has accepted
his fate.
Stop!
This does not
concern you.
There is no hope.
No!
Hope lives.
It is everywhere.
I've seen it,
everyone you have touched,
the people
you have helped.
You saved them!
Enough!
Hope is just
a fleeting sentiment.
Your failure is real.
You must face the consequences
or continue to bear the guilt of
your dishonor for all eternity.
Jack, don't listen!
You're being misguided!
I've seen it.
You've saved
countless innocents.
And most of all...
...you showed me the truth!
You made me see
that there's so much more to me
than I knew existed.
You made me way more
than what I was.
The hope you gave me
saved my life!
Death follows in your wake --
men, woman, children.
Yes.
All those children dead
because of you.
No!
The children -- they're alive!
You saved them!
No more words!
I, uh...
I like your hair.
And dress.
What now?
It's time
to find my sword.
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Back to the past,
Samurai Jack *
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Got to get back,
back to the past *
* Samurai Jack
* Watch out
* Jack, Jack,
Jack, Jack, Jack *
* Watch out
* Got to get back
* Samurai Jack
* Jack, Jack, Jack
* Wa-Watch out
* Jack, Jack, Jack, Jack